Thank you for watching!
I always dream of being a boy
And always with you
A-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a
I wonder if I'll be able to get the results
I don't have to be with you like that
The time when I was young is
There's a picture of you
You and you and you
If you love me,
I'll be the one and only person
I don't want to be the one with you
Are you ready?
I got a serious feeling!
If I had to make a mistake, I would have been so angry that I would have become a big fan of this!
We were told that we were going to a different world!
I don't know where this is going and why I don't know where this is going to be going!
What will happen if I get this?
Today's picnic!
Ah...!
HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA
Uwaa...
Why does it hurt?
I can't believe it!!!
You're already dead!
Come on!
Wow…forgive me…
Is your armor shot great?
It's like it doesn't fit me perfectly…
Do I have to give you a hell of a hand…
It's gonna be fascial on your legs!
Stop it, I'm the one who came to you.
That's right.
Huh?
You're going to raise this for the next day?
Oh, no.
Hey, don't worry.
I'm going to find you.
Huh? Are you a witch?
I was so happy that I couldn't do anything about it.
What are you saying?
I'm glad that you gave me this kind of advice.
That's right.
I'll be back in a few days.
What do you want?
G-Gokiburi!
Gokiburi?
Gokiburi!
I'm so happy that I can't do anything about it.
I'll be back in a few days.
Ria!
What?
I like it.
Ueba!
Could I do it?
You, too?
Yeah, that's a big thing.
It's just me and Ria.
I have a question for you.
I'm so happy that I can't do anything about it.
Hey, you idiot!
It's all about making friends.
Right! What are you doing?
What is it? I was thinking about making videos about making friends.
It's okay, I know.
If you go to the research center, you won't be able to move your hand.
Then, what are you doing?
I'm going to go ahead.
Ah, that's right.
Why?
Are you going to go ahead and go ahead?
Ah, that's right.
I'm going to go ahead.
No, no, no.
You're not going to be able to go ahead with us, aren't you?
Huh?
No, no, no, no, no!
How do I do this?
I'm going to use my hand.
Ah, I'm going to cry.
Ah!
Is this scary?
If you eat poison and eat poison,
you'll be able to go ahead.
You're going to go?
Really?
You're not going to be able to go ahead again, aren't you?
You're not going to be able to go ahead.
I'm going to cry.
That's not it.
Hey, everyone!
The Uroo-roo is not going to be able to go ahead.
Ah, Rock and paper.
Uroo-roo, you're going to go ahead and go ahead and go ahead.
Then, really?
I'm going to go to the picnic in the night.
I'm going to go to the top.
I did it!
I'm going to go to the top!
I'm going to go!
Please be careful.
I won't come back soon.
I'm going to go to the picnic in the night.
The picnic in the night?
I'm going to the picnic in the night.
Where?
I don't have to go to the toilet.
I'm going torest on the eastmost.
Oh, my God!
Let's go over here!
Wait, wait!
Why do you keep on collecting props from the kitchen?
주nda is going to collect these!
I believe her age is different from Marui go Last or last But it's not.
Okay.
She wants to fall asleep while on her way to the BÜNDNISokarms hanger.
Don't say your words!
It's okay.
This looks like it's going to be a mix of all sorts of things.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Ranca-san.
It's been a long time since I've been here.
I can't leave you alone anymore.
I'm going to have a dinner with you in front of you before you leave me.
Let's go!
Ah!
I love you!
I love this much!
Really, it's a picnic…
Um…
Something's different!
Ugh…
That's terrible!
Hey, don't touch me!
I'm not even happy yet, baby!
U-Huh?
I-I'm not...
Now, the co-cati,
if you eat it, it makes you feel great!
Ume-nen-chan, open it!
Aaaaaaah!
Yo-yo!
Aaaaaah!
Don't cry!
This is a girl, a woman, a woman, a woman!
A woman, a woman, a woman, a woman!
Yo-no, are you okay?
Huh?
Aaaaaah!
I can do it! I can do it!
I'm dangerous!
Yo-yo!
What?
No!
It's been a long time since I've done it.
Mide!
Rock and roll!
Nika-Nika!
I'm nervous!
I'm going to pick up a picnic from now on.
I'm nervous.
Really!
I'm nervous!
Look!
I'll see you again tomorrow morning!
Yo-yo!
I'm nervous!
Um...
Hello?
Looks like this is the wrong place.
Nika-Nika...
I'm...
I can't believe it.
Eh?
Are you here?
Baby!
This is a great gift.
I'm sure you can take it from me.
Eh?
You don't have to take it from me, right?
I'm sure you can take it from me!
I got it!
Wow!
Yo-yo!
It's been a long time since I've done it.
Well,
I'll take it from you first.
Nika-Nika...
Oh!
Are you sure you can take it from me?
Huh?
I got it!
Don't do it! Don't do it!
Don't do it!
I got it!
Baby!
Yeah!
I'm sure you can take it from me.
Nika-Nika...
Eh?
Are you sure you can take it from me?
Huh?
If you go back, I'll be able to give it to you!
Ah, I see!
Six?
What is it?
I'm sure you can take it from me.
Are you sure you can take it from me?
When I take this box,
I'm sure you can take it from me.
You want to save it?
Hey!
I'm sure you can take it from me.
Come on, go!
It's not that easy for me to do this.
I'm sure you can take it from me.
Hurry up!
Hey, go!
I feel bad.
What's wrong with you?
You can take it from me.
I can take it from me.
A spider will help you get off you.
Hey!
What are you doing?
You're using your own hands!
Hey!
Well, that guy is a tough guy!
You!
Hey!
Iseneca there?!
onto him!
Please, don't run!
It's a lunge!
Look at him!
Doesn't seem like he is clever.
He's like a boy!
It was his rival.
Maybe.
Drunk!
Look!
He got scared!
Baby!
zwycyity!
I said it!
Alright, let's talk, baby!
Uh-huh!
Guys, what's the worst?
I'm going to be a hero!
Why are you still standing there?
I was just kidding!
Yeah!
I mean, I finally went to the top of the mountain,
but I'm getting tired of these things.
Hey, I'm crying.
Really, this is the best place to be!
Oh, I see.
What? What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I forgot.
This guy is so funny.
What?
What's the lock?
I've put it up to the top of my head.
What?
Then, just the lock.
What do you mean?
I'm back.
How did you get here?
Do you remember anyone?
Yes.
I wish I could get out of here.
I don't think I could get out of here.
Why?
Why do you want me to go to the mountain?
I don't know.
But I told you.
What should I do?
Don't you believe in me?
Hey, are you mad?
Oh, I don't know.
I can't get out of here.
Don't you believe in me?
It's been a week.
You.
Get out of here.
What's wrong?
I'm waiting.
Get out of here.
Where is everyone?
I'm glau à la Looking.
I'm glau à la Looking!
Are you OK?
Shall we go?
Are you okay?
Are you OK?
Makan that's up!
I do!
Well, I felt like I'm walking far from here.
We came to find a little girl's special treasure.
This is so much fun!
I don't know how to do it.
I don't even know how to find the way back.
This?
No more!
You're so close!
It's just that you can use it to be on your way home.
But you can't come to help anyone if you're here.
Buh-ha!
I don't want to die like this!
I'll save you!
Please, help me!
God, God, God, God, God, God, God, God...
Help us!
What's going on?
It's quiet.
What?
Are we dreaming?
Yeah, we're dreaming!
Yeah.
Huh? We're dreaming!
Ulul!
Nika Nika!
Yeah, right?
There's a lot of fun, Ulul.
Ulul?
Huh?
Then, where is this?
Well, this is the place where we're going to sleep.
Here we go!
Well, we're going to sleep tonight.
We're going to sleep tonight.
It's a lot of fun, Ulul.
Well, we're going to sleep tonight.
Yeah, right.
Ulul, Ulul.
Ulul!
It's me,你的 baby.
Do you think we're going to sleep at this red light tonight!?
What are you doing!?
It's a little too small for an emergency, but how can we get out of here?
There's a lot of fun, Ulul.
We have the wall!
Ooh!
Here, come here.
Where should we get the wall?
Errry?
I thought it was from here, Ulul.
I don't know where the wall is either!
Oh, no!
Oh, no! This is where it is!
Oh, here, here!
There's something I wanted to see!
Oh, no!
Isn't this the place where the shop is located?
That's right!
It's always around here, isn't it?
Yes!
Hurry up, Chitaro Baby!
Well, now that you're in the middle of the mountain,
That's right!
Oh, no! I'm back!
I lost!
Oh, no!
There's something on top of it!
Is it heavy?
Let's go!
Chitaro Baby!
Yay!
Oh, no!
What's going on?
What?
Oh, it's heavy!
Oh, no!
I'm so scared that I'll fall in love with you!
Look, this crab is delicious!
What?
Oh, no!
I'm going to lose!
I'm going to die!
Oh, no!
Wow!
Look at this!
Who is it?
Please go home early!
Oh, no!
The rain is always there
The voice is ringing, the sound is ringing
HEN, HEN, NAKYATSU
Our, what's this?
It's the next round
Televerse, the middle of the story
It's a heart
Bye!
Party!
Let's go!
Pretty!
Everybody's love